trinasolar.com 2013-05-22

# Trina Solar

## Privacy Policy

Trina Solar issues this privacy policy as its commitment on protecting the privacy of every individual or company. This statement outlines the policy to protect the personal information you provide us when visiting the Site.

### Information Collection

We may require you to provide individual identifiable and background information for the convenience of your visiting or for providing you services after visiting the Site. You reserve the right of offering your confidential data to the Site. And if you do not want your confidential data collected, please do not submit it to us. We may collect the domain names, not the e-mail addresses, of visitors and we also seek to place a "cookie" on your computer's hard drive which allows the server to determine the computer when it visits again, in order to track statistical information about navigation to and throughout certain areas of our site. This is used to help us improve our site navigation and to measure the effectiveness of our overall website experience.

### Information Use

Providing us with your personal information makes it easier for us to make our website relevant to you, communicate with you, assist you in making a purchase of our products, and allow you access to certain limited-entry areas of our site.

The personal information you provide us may be stored and processed in which we or any affiliates conduct operations. By submitting such information, you consent to the transfer of such information outside your home country.

### Information Security

The site will strictly manage and protect the personal data you offer to us. And your personal information will be kept confidential unless you clearly state in the relevant part of the Site that you agree to expose one or some parts of your personal information. Any information about you will not be exposed or sold to the third party.

Except the confidential data explicitly stated, any other information you provide to the Site, including problems, suggestions, opinions or the like will not be regarded as confidential.

### Links to Other Sites

Trina Solar's website contains links to other sites, and we are not responsible for the information collection or privacy practices, or the content on those sites.

### Changes to this Policy

Please check this privacy policy periodically to inform yourself of any changes.
